WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Oh my God!
Oh my God! What happened? What happened?
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna get her back to Durham,
and she's gonna be happy.
She's gonna live a normal
life like the rest of us.
'Kay?
I'm not worried in the slightest.
Oh, good.
Yeah, I know.
It wasn't that bad 'cause it was...
Pornchai.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Pornchai!
Hey, baby!
I'm sorry.
Thank you. Hi.
Didn't expect you so early.
- Yeah. Do you need a minute?
- Mm-hm. Yeah.
- Okay. Okay. I'm so sorry.
- Yep. Yep.
No, no, no. Don't be
sorry. Don't be sorry. No.
Why do you sound so
mad? What's the problem?
I just... To be honest,
I can't believe you took the
boat and went without me.
Gary, are you fucking kidding?
I invited you. I wanted you to come.
Well, that seems to
be the case with you.
You know, you do whatever
you want without me.
Oh my God. Gary, stop.
Not right now. Are you kidding me?
You know what? I
don't want to talk about it
right now either. I'm... I'm over it.
- I'll just see you later.
- Oh, Ga... Gary!
Are you fucking kidding me?
- Oh my God.
- What's happened?
He thinks I hooked up
with one of the brothers.
Did you?
No.
I hooked up with both of them.
Gary's gonna dump me.
Or worse. I don't know.
Oh, Chloe, you're beautiful.
You're a Libra rising, for God's sake.
That makes you a quality person.
There are way better
options out there than Gary.
I don't want another option.
I... I don't want to have
to go back out there
and find someone else.
I... I know I complain
about him a lot, but...
but this is a good situation.
I gotta bribe the deckhands,
so they don't rat me out.
Hey.
Hi! How's Bangkok?
What did you do last night?
I met up with an old friend.
Oh, yeah? You guys go out?
No.
Yeah, right. I called
you. You didn't answer.
I didn't do anything. My buddy is sober.
So fucking annoying.
Oh, yeah, it must be so annoying,
me caring about you.
How do you stand it?
Please come back.
I'm gonna come back tomorrow.
- Bad luck comes in threes.
- Jesus Christ.
I don't want anything bad to happen.
I can't remember last night, at all.
We both blacked out.
You okay?
I love you. Put the "I" in front of it.
"I love you." Not "love ya."
Well... it's just...
it's different, isn't it?
It means something different.
So...
So...?
I think there was a little sleepover.
I thought I heard some
noises in the night,
and then this morning,
who do I see walking past
my room in the same clothes
he was wearing yesterday?
Valentin.
What do you mean?
I mean...
He slept over... with Jaclyn?
- Hey, babe.
- Hey, you.
- Where've you been?
- Yeah, I was on set,
and my phone died. You know how it is.
- Uh-huh.
- It's been crazy here.
Do you see how crazy this is?
Do you see how she
was pushing him on me?
And all the time, she wanted him.
She has not changed at all.
She's exactly the same. It's so psycho.
So, what are you up to?
You even miss me at all?
- Yes, of course I miss you.
- You better.
Just glad you finally
charged your phone.
- Is that right?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm so fucking horny for you.
- Stop.
- I am. I am!
It's sad. She's an aging actress.
You saw her yesterday.
She literally lives off male attention.
It's one thing when you're
25. But... now you're 45,
and guess what? It's pathetic.
I didn't think you were
gonna care so much.
I don't care. I don't.
It's not like I was into him.
She just kept pushing the idea.
Do you remember all
the times she did that?
- I do.
- Talking about how I'm the only single one,
how I should hook up
with him. It's demented.
I... I just thought you
were gonna laugh about it.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm laughing. It's funny.
Ha! But also...
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
What?
- Hey!
- How are you doing, ladies?
- Hi.
- You feel okay?
I'm okay. Not a hundred percent.
- Well, did you enjoy last night?
- I loved it!
Loved meeting your friends.
Ooh, that Vlad.
Golly, he's been through a lot.
He's a little crazy.
But him and Aleksei,
they're just my oldest friends.
Yeah. Did you have a good time?
I loved dancing with Laurie.
Jaclyn's not having breakfast?
Hmm. I think she had a late night.
Shall I book anything at the spa today?
It's okay. I don't want anything.
And tonight, we talked about
going to the Muay Thai fights.
Hmm. I think I'm just
gonna stay around the hotel.
Yeah.
You know how to reach me
if you need anything at all.
- Have a wonderful day.
- Thanks, Valentin.
I don't know how it happened.
One minute, he was helping
me get this lizard out of my room,
and the next minute,
we were in bed, and...
God.
I'm happy for you, okay?
I'm glad you're getting a
little somethin' somethin'.
- Hmm.
- You know, it just feels like...
I just feel like everyone's
getting action except me.
Uh, you might be an adult,
but I'm still your mother.
- I don't wanna hear that shit.
- Okay, Mom, all I do is study.
- And I'm stressed the F out.
- Look. First, you get the money.
Then you get the power.
Then you get the woman. Okay?
- Scarface?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
So, what, you're getting
gangster on me now?
Gotta get gangster around here.
Well, why is that?
I'll tell you later.
Can you just... Just tell me now.
- Morning!
- Good morning.
Feeling better about everything today?
Not really. Fabian,
this is my son, Zion.
He's just visiting. Fabian
is our general manager.
- Okay.
- Hello.
Hi.
I'm inviting a few of the
staff to the restaurant tonight.
I wanted to include you.
I'm going to...
Yes, I think I'm going to sing.
- Okay.
- I'm quite nervous,
- but excited.
- Yeah.
I will try to be there. So...
So, break a leg, 'kay?
Both of 'em, all right?
Yeah, yes. Thank you.
- Yes. Of course.
- Yeah.
Mr. and Mrs. Schroeder, guten morgen.
Morning, boys.
- Hey, what's up?
- You're hungover.
How was your full moon party?
I mean,
it was like a lot of
lasers and shitty music.
There's something you both should know.
Your sister has no thesis.
We're really here because
she wants to move to Thailand
so she can study under some guru.
What?
So, your father and I are
going over to his compound
this morning to make
sure it's not a cult.
It's not a cult!
What, you're gonna move to Thailand?
What do you care?
Because you're my little sister.
Okay? I don't wanna see
you wasting away your life.
Right,
and gambling with other people's money,
that's not wasting your
life. That's meaningful.
Uh, I think it sounds kinda cool.
Like, sounds like it'd
be a good experience.
I mean, it's only a year.
That guy's written some good books.
Name one. Buddhism for Dipshits?
If that strange man is
going to have my baby,
he'd better be the
best Buddhist in China.
- What?
- Saxon!
Jesus, Mary, and
Joseph! Turn that thing off!
Timothy!
Timothy, let's go!
- Oh, God.
- Come on, let's go.
Lochlan. Will you please come?
Please?
Yeah, of course.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I just...
- I gotta, like, change.
- Yeah.
Put some clothes on, you know the drill.
Okay. Thank you.
Okay, dude, I'll see you later.
Hey.
- I missed you.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yes, I did.
- Hmm.
You fucked one of those brothers.
What?
- How was it?
- Oh my God, Gary.
They're like little boys.
Liar.
No, I swear.
Just tell me what you did.
We did nothing, okay? We
just... We just partied. It was stupid.
Tell me you did it.
Tell me which one you fucked.
Why? Is that what you want, or...?
Bring him over tonight.
Why?
I wanna have people over tonight.
Like a party or something?
I need to deal with something,
and I need your help.
- Hi.
Uh... Belinda?
Everything okay with your son?
He'll probably hold it over
me for the rest of my life.
- Oh my God.
- But I got stuff on him too.
I'm sorry.
No. I wanted you to stay.
Uh, Belinda?
You told me you had a dream
of having your own
business, your own spa, right?
And I was thinking...
that's something, uh...
we could do together.
And, you know, if we did it in Thailand,
not as difficult.
Well, it's... it's
definitely still a dream.
Yeah, so we should talk about
it later when you have time.
Oh, my client's coming.
Sawatdee khrap. Please, have seats.
- Thank you.
- Please.
Here's our menu.
Ah!
Wow, you look so beautiful.
Thank you.
- Sawatdee kha.
- Sawatdee khrap.
This place is very popular.
- Mmm. I know the owner.
- Oh.
His father has a
billion-dollar tuna business.
- Hmm.
- So, the seafood here is...
...good.
Oh.
Where is your friend, the director?
I just got off the phone with him.
He is very excited to meet you.
He's been watching
all of your old movies.
Which movies?
You know, he didn't say, actually.
But, um... But he did tell me
that he thinks you're fantastic.
The movies are not that good.
Which ones, I wonder?
What matters is he really likes you.
And I... I really hope that this
is not gonna be an imposition,
but because the film
is still being written,
and your part, uh, the woman
that you would be playing,
your character, would
be very similar to you.
Similar to me? Does he know me?
He wants to get to know you better,
which would inspire him
to write a great part for you.
And he thinks the best way to do that
would be to meet at your house...
you know, so he could
observe you in your...
habitat.
He wants to meet me in my habitat?
That's his preference, yeah.
Well...
...why didn't you tell me this
before I came all the way here?
I'm sorry. I mean, he just called.
Geniuses, right? What are you gonna do?
Well... my husband is at my house.
And he is not well.
Well, we wouldn't bother him.
We'd just come by for a quick drink.
A quick drink?
Sritala...
it's a big Hollywood production.
I would love for you to be a part of it.
Sawatdee kha.
Hi, uh, I think I have an appointment
with Luang Por Teera.
I... I know I'm a little bit early,
but is that o... is that okay?
- It's okay.
- Okay.
You just go in that door.
He is in that building on the right.
Oh, great. Okay. Thank you so much.
Um, I'll be right back.
Just s... stay here.
Hi. Sawatdee kha.
I was told I could come
in here. Is it okay that I sit?
- Please.
- Okay, thank you.
Wow. I'm, uh, I'm... I'm
so honored to meet you.
I'm coming back this
summer for the intensive,
but I just wanted to sit with you
for a few minutes if that's okay.
I've been feeling a little lost.
Lately, it's felt like...
everything is pointless...
and the things my family cares about,
I just don't care about, you know?
I just don't.
And your books have really helped me
get through some really bad days,
so thank you for that.
Um...
Anyway, they're...
they're here, my parents.
They're out in the courtyard.
And I wanted to talk to you,
but I think it would be better
if you talked to them instead.
Otherwise, they're not
gonna let me come here.
I... I mean, I... I could still come.
I'm an adult, obviously,
but they could just
make it so difficult that it...
it would... it just would be bad.
Sorry, I've...
I've been so excited to meet you,
and this is not how I wanted this to go,
but, um...
do you think you
could just sit with them
for a few minutes?
They'll probably ask
some really basic questions.
They don't really know
anything about this.
But... And... and my mom is...
Well, you'll see.
But would that be okay?
Bring in your parents. I
can answer their questions.
Thank you. Thank you
so much. Khop khun kha.
Where's Mom?
I think she wanted to walk around.
But he's ready to talk to
y'all. He's in there waiting.
Oh, well, she wanted
me to talk to him anyway.
Where did she go?
I'm Victoria Ratliff. Okay.
- Nice to meet you.
- Oh my God.
Is... Will my daughter be safe?
- I don't really talk...
- Hi!
Sawatdee kha. How are you?
They don't... They're
not talking at all.
That's okay. We're gonna walk over here.
- Khop khun kha.
- They don't speak English.
Um...
Oh.
- Sawatdee khrap.
Sawatdee kha.
Mmm.
You all right?
Yeah. Just my serotonin
levels are a little low.
- You seem freaked out.
- No, I don't.
What, do I? No, I'm fine.
'Kay.
I just don't understand why
you wouldn't hook up with me.
Because I have a boyfriend.
Whatever.
And he's my soulmate.
What does that even mean?
Once you've connected with someone
on a spiritual level, you
can't go back to cheap sex.
Hooking up with you would
be an empty experience.
And how would you know that?
Because I know. Because you're soulless.
Sad.
You have questions for me?
Well, my daughter
wants to join your... your...
Mmm. Whatever this is.
And, uh...
And you want to understand why?
Yeah.
Many young people come
here from your country.
I think because,
maybe, spiritual malaise.
Lost connection with
nature, with the family.
Lost connection with the spirit.
What is left?
The self. Identity.
Chasing money, pleasure. Yeah?
Everyone run from pain
towards the pleasure.
But when they get there,
only to find more pain.
You cannot outrun pain.
Yeah.
Okay. Thanks.
Yeah, can... can I ask
you one more question?
What do...
What do you think happens...
when we die?
When we die? Great question.
When you're born,
you are like a single drop of water,
flying upward,
separated from the
one, giant consciousness.
You get older. You descend back down.
You die.
You land back into the water,
become one with the ocean again.
No more separated. No more suffering.
One consciousness.
Death is a happy
return, like coming home.
Oh...
Thank you.
I have to say something.
I can't just not say anything.
Why? Why do you have to?
Because it just feels fake.
One person's fake
is another person's,
you know, good manners.
We're all friends. It's whatever.
She can do what she
wants. It's not a big deal.
Not a good idea.
What are you guys talking about?
Oh, we're just talking about, um...
our kids.
We know about Valentin.
What about him?
That he spent the night.
So, how was it?
Nothing happened.
He came over for a while, but then...
You're so funny.
What do you mean?
You're just funny.
So, what?
You and Harrison have an
open relationship or something?
No.
Okay, well...
Well, don't worry. It's like you said.
What happened in
Thailand stays in Thailand.
I told you nothing happened.
Jaclyn, get real.
Okay, I need a drink.
Excuse me. Can we get
three margaritas, please?
Oh, just two. I don't need one.
Shut up, Kate. Have
a drink for fuck's sake.
Can I ask, and I'm just curious,
why did you keep pushing him on me
when it was always your plan
to hook up with him yourself?
Are you crazy?
I never had a plan to do anything.
I don't care. I'm just curious.
Whatever, Laurie.
You're not just curious.
You're obviously mad about something.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
be coming at me like this.
I don't know. When
Kate told me she saw him
coming out of your room
this morning... You did.
It just made me laugh. It's like...
it's like nobody ever changes.
We're still the same people
we were in the tenth grade.
It's just funny. It's funny.
I'm not sure what that means, but okay.
This is what you always did.
Never mind.
Forget it. It doesn't matter.
What?
Well? What was it like? What did he say?
I liked him.
He seemed legitimate, you know?
I should've gone with you.
Mom, you're just gonna have to accept
that this is happening,
and I'm doing this,
and it's not the worst
thing in the world.
You think that now,
but once you get here,
you're not going to like it.
- Oh, really?
- Mm-hmm.
I will support it.
Well, I won't support it, but
I will keep my mouth shut
if you stay here for one night.
Stay here tonight, sleep
here, and if you still think
this is a place where you
want to spend a whole year,
then do it. La-di-da.
Okay. Yeah.
Perfect. Wonderful.
I don't know if they'll let
me or if they have room.
Oh, they have room.
How do you know?
Because I did a whole
tour, and I saw how they live.
It's... it's grim.
So, you want me to go
ask if I can spend the night?
Yeah.
And if I still wanna do
this, you will support me?
Yes, absolutely.
Okay. I'll go talk to them.
I'll stay with you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you.
That's a...
That's a brutal story.
So, can you help me out here?
I'd love to help you out, man.
I'm tryna live a different
kind of life here, brother.
Frank, it's not gonna get messy.
You're gonna kill the dude, right?
In my book, that's a little messy.
I'm not gonna kill him. I'm not.
Why'd you ask for the gun, then?
I won't even bring it,
okay? I won't bring it.
I just need ten minutes with the guy.
I need for him to know
how bad he fucked me up.
And I need your help.
Please.
Lek.
Oh.
Why would you encourage her to move
to a monastery?
What's next?
You want her to shave her
head and start banging a bongo
in Times Square?
I think it'd be a good
experience for her
to live for a while
without all the creature
comforts that she's used to.
I don't want her
thinking she'll be just fine
if she's poor.
She needs to fear poverty,
Tim, like everyone else we know.
That way, she'll make good decisions.
And we want our kids
to be tough, don't we?
Resilient. You know? Just...
W... what if we lost everything?
We're not gonna lose everything.
- No.
- No. And if we did,
honestly, I don't
know if I'd wanna live.
Why would you say that?
What does that mean?
I just don't think...
at this age, I'm meant to
live an uncomfortable life.
I don't have the will.
You do. Sure you do.
- No.
- No?
No. I just don't have it in me.
I don't think I ever did.
I like my scents. Mmm. I like my velvet.
Grass. Tuberose.
- Oh, hey.
- How did it go?
- I'm not sure.
He knows about you.
Me?
B... but how does he know about me?
Well, I basically told him.
He asked me point-blank.
I can't just lie to his face.
What do you mean? Yes, you can.
- Of course you can.
- He doesn't seem that mad.
He doesn't?
You should come to the house tonight,
both of you. We're having people over.
- It's gonna be fun.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I'm not gonna go there
if he thinks that I hooked up with you.
He doesn't care.
Okay? He invited you.
I thought he'd be jealous too,
but for some reason, he's not.
He seemed kind of, like...
turned on or something.
Hey, maybe he wants a threesome.
- Oh.
- A threesome?
You've never had a threesome before?
Well, yeah. I mean, of course,
but not with another guy.
Hmm.
What about last night?
That wasn't a... I mean,
it wasn't a threesome.
What, are you kidding me?
That was my little brother.
Yeah, and you guys made out.
- That was a joke.
- What part was a joke?
You guys forced us to.
I didn't force him to jerk you off.
What do you mean? That never happened.
What? I don't remember that.
Well, I blacked out.
Well, I didn't. So...
Oh, shit.
Oh, that fucking drug.
What the fuck did you give us anyway?
God, I don't think
there's a drug in the world
that would make me get with my brother.
Hey, I don't judge, okay?
Yeah, I mean, it's fine.
Everyone has their thing.
- It's fine.
- Don't... It's not a thing.
It's not a thing. It's
definitely not a thing.
Okay? It's not.
- Okay.
- Okay, let's just...
Let's just forget about it, please.
Seriously.
As long as you come for dinner tonight.
Wh... You know what?
I'm actually just gonna
go back to my room.
I'll see you guys later.
- Yeah, see you tonight.
- Bring your brother.
What?
Okay. So, when are we
gonna meet for dinner?
Are we going to the Muay Thai fight?
- No.
Aw, we said last night we were gonna go.
You told him this morning
you weren't gonna go.
I think we should. It'll
be fun. And a lot of, like,
sweaty, ripped guys,
testosterone in the air.
Come on. Valentin will be there.
- Laurie, fuck off. Mm-hmm?
- Hmm.
- Laurie, what are you doing?
What am I doing? What am I doing?
- Why are you antagonizing her?
- Look, I'm not like you.
Sometimes I just have to be honest.
Oh, you know what I mean.
I'll see you at 7:00.
Hmm.
Hey.
Listen, she's drunk.
Do you know how much
gossip I have to deal with?
And then, like, my own friends,
the few people that I think
I can trust are talking shit
about me behind my back.
It's really depressing.
Jaclyn, that's not exact...
Let's shut down our monkey mind. Yes?
Close your eyes.
As thoughts emerge...
acknowledge them.
Say hello.
- Yeah. It gets better.
- Okay.
And very gently, let them go. Goodbye.
Breathe in...
hold it...
and breathe out.
Mmm.
Ah. Sorry.
How are you?
- Remember me?
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, I live right up the hill.
- Huh.
- Yeah.
We're having some people
over tonight for dinner. I thought...
I know it's last minute, but
maybe you'd wanna come.
That's so nice. But my son,
he's, uh, he's visiting, so...
Oh, bring him.
He's, um, pretty
jet-lagged. He just flew in.
I think we should talk.
Okay.
Last house, top of
the hill. Come any time.
Thank you so much.
Hey.
What is it?
I love you.
- Dad.
- Hey.
Hey. Where is everyone?
Uh, your mother's napping.
And, uh, Locher and Pipelan are...
are staying with the monks.
Locher and Pipelan?
What's up?
Uh, we just got invited to
go to some dinner party, but...
I don't know. Maybe
it's not a good idea.
I mean, you seem like...
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Uh, a dinner party sounds fun. Yeah.
I... I'll go wake your mother.
Okay.
Oh, shit. What the fuck?
Yeah. Nice to see ya.
Hey. All right.
Peace. Peace.
- Hey.
- Welcome.
Sawatdee khrap.
The mysterious Steve. I'm Sritala.
Yes, you are. Great to
meet you. Such a fan.
Thank you for having us.
And this is my husband, Khun Jim.
- How are ya?
- Hello, sir.
- How are you?
- This way.
Magnificent house you have here.
Oh, thank you.
- Synced and corrected by actumaxime -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -